Secret Millionaire is a romance, tv movie film directed by Michael M. Scott.
When a bored millionaire (Steve Lund) is mistaken for a parking attendant by a beautiful girl (Siobhan Williams) who is protesting
against his family’s intention of closing a local park, he uses the misunderstanding to get to know her better.
Sean Payton, played by Steve Lund.
Alisson, played by Siobhan Williams.
Jared, played by Jaime M. Callica.
Caden, played by Adam DiMarco.
Candice, played by Elise Gatien.
Joe Millionaire is an American reality television series
broadcast by the Fox Broadcasting Company (Fox).
The series premiered on January 6, 2003, and concluded with the
finale of its second season on November 24, 2003.
Both seasons followed a group of single women in
competition for the affection of a bachelor.
The women were under the belief that the bachelor was a millionaire;
however, he was actually a working class average Joe.
If the final remaining woman still accepted the bachelor after
learning about the ruse, the two split a $1,000,000 reward.
The series was hosted by American television presenter Alex McLeod.
The first season of Joe Millionaire experienced high success in ratings, with its season finale being the highest-rated
entertainment program (excluding Super Bowl lead-out programs) aired on network television since 2000.
The second season, titled The Next Joe Millionaire,
experienced disappointing ratings throughout its run.
In 2005, Joe Millionaire and The Next Joe Millionaire were among several television programs cited in a
class-action lawsuit filed by the Writers Guild of America concerning labor law violations.
In November 2021, Fox announced a revival entitled Joe Millionaire: For
Richer or Poorer, which aired from January 6 to March 10, 2022.
The revival featured two bachelors, one a working-class
man and the other a secret millionaire.
The tone is emotional.